

25 VIA LUCCA APT. J233, Irvine, CA 92612 | C: (626)425-1696 | syui0128@gmail.com

July 18th, 2017

Taco Bell Corp.

RE: Analyst, Strategic Development & Analysis

Dear Hiring Manager,

It is with great interest that I am forwarding my resume for consideration as an **Analyst** at the Irvine office. Given my diverse background in Strategic Development and Data Analysis, I believe I will be an excellent fit for this opportunity. Please consider the following highlights from my resume:

- Worked in a strategy consulting company, with highly professional skills of Strategy Planning, Data Analysis (advanced Excel knowledge) and Presentation/Report Preparation (Proficient at making and interpreting analysis into PowerPoint).
- Exceptional communicator demonstrated by being a successful art salesperson, also, with experience communicating with all levels of management from different client companies for extracting accurate company insights.
- Familiar with financial evaluation (analyzing financial data, projecting incomes, modeling returns etc.) by working with private funds on due diligence projects.
- Delivered professional strategy plans by being in a team which carefully analyzed all sorts of internal and external data, applied analysis to business frameworks/knowledge, identified company issues, discovered business opportunities, and interpreted the results in a straight forward and yet reader friendly way.
- Achieved the online channel ROI of 147% for a start-up company.
- A highly motivated and adaptable fast learner, have quickly mastered different tasks as a new position required

Given my experience and competencies, I am confident that I would be a great addition to the team. My excellent organizational and interpersonal skills have assisted me in striving in both team-oriented and self-directed environments.

cere	

Suey Yu



CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Comprehensive Data Analysis (Advanced Excel Skills)
- Professional Business Strategy Developing
- Excellent Report Writing Skills (Proficient in PowerPoint)
- Outstanding Communication skills
- Strong at Numbers and Logical Thinking
- Multilingual (English/Cantonese/Mandarin/Japanese)

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

03/2017 to Present

Fine Art Consultant

Ning Zhou Gallery—Laguna Beach, CA, the United States

Bringing in sales by influencing diverse customers with smooth communications and careful follow-ups.

07/2013 to 04/2016

Online Channel General Manager

Glamorous Apparel Limited — Zhaoqing, GuangDong, China

- Developed and implemented online strategies based on knowledge of company objectives, data analysis and market trends, achieved the ROI of 147%
- Supported company executives, recruited and managed an online marketing/sale team of 15 employees, launched an Alibaba Tmall store, cultivated and successfully maintained partnerships with 5 other online shopping websites throughout Asia

07/2010 to 01/2013

Analyst

P&E Directions — Tokyo, Tokyo, Japan

- Performed well under multiple demanding, deadline-driven business consulting projects including strategy planning, due diligence etc., responsible for market research, data analysis and presentation writing.
- Successfully extracted company insights by effectively communicating and interviewing with all levels of management of client companies.
- Designed 3 consumer surveys, held over 20 focus group interviews, finished 100+ store investigations, analyzed the massive raw data, identified issues and discovered opportunities, then interpreted into insightful and professional PowerPoint presentations.
- Worked with private funds to analyze acquired parties' internal data (e.g. financial sheets) and external market data, project incomes and ROI modeling.
- Won an internal "cross nations new business idea" contest, resulted in helping the company getting a due diligence project on a second-hand luxury product retail company

EDUCATION

2012

Bachelor of Science: ECONOMICS

Yokohama city university — Yokohama, Kanagawa, Japan